

Ilya Zaitsev Frontend Engineer

Contacts



Email

godested@gmail.com



Phone

+380 63 400 6684



Location

Kyiv, Ukraine

Socials



LinkedIn





witter





Instagram





GitHub

@godested



CodeWars

@godested

Languages



English

Upper-Intermediate



Ukrainian/Russian

Native

Professional summary

Passionate frontend engineer with more than 5 years of commercial experience. Good at project development from scratch and improvement of existing solutions. Have analytical and problem-solving skills. Confidently understand how to build an MVP. Able to create full autonomy in frontend development. Strive to improve DX, automate code quality analysis. Familiar with unit economics. Ready to analyze business requirements, propose product and development flow improvements.

Looking for a professional workgroup to implement knowledge and gained experience, be a part of the "Big idea" project, grow and contribute, improve management and product skills to obtain a lead position in the future.

Experience



Playtech · Live

Senior Frontend Engineer

Aug 2020 - Present · 1 yr 8 mos

• Kyiv, Ukraine

Developed and launched 5 multi-screen games. Took responsibility for code review, improving DX, refactoring of existing solutions, developing new big features.

TypeScript, React, Mobx, RxJS, Inversify, Webpack, Protobuf, Jest, Kibana, Jonkins



Genesis

Senior Frontend Engineer

Feb 2019 - Aug 2020 · 1 yr 7 mos

• Kyiv, Ukraine

Successfully launched social app, brand landings. Further evolution to full-fledged product (with support, analytics, payments) was made. Had active participation in the hiring of technical specialists as a interviewer for various projects. Was a mentor for junior developers.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, Gatsby, TypeScript, WebSockets, GitLab CI/CD, Docker, Sentry, PRPL pattern.



Skywell Software

Frontend Developer

Oct 2018 - Feb 2019 · 5 mos

Kyiv, Ukraine

In collaboration with a back-end developer, successfully developed an application based on UX mockups.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, CMMN, BPMN, Docker.



Lab73

Frontend Developer

Apr 2018 - Oct 2018 · 7 mos

• Kyiv, Ukraine

Developed service for searching closest money exchangers with a favorable rate. Mobile-first, cross-browser and SEO friendly app. Developed service with real-time calls, pptx presentations and schedule manager.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, CMMN, BPMN, Docker.



WorkRocks

Frontend Developer

Jan 2018 - May 2018 · 4 mos

Onipro, Ukraine

Developed real-time crypto-currencies exchange MVP.
React, Redux, TypeScript, WebSockets, Node.js.



Freelance (With Mentor)
Frontend Developer

Feb 2017 - Apr 2018 · 1 yr 3 mos

• Dnipro, Ukraine

Developed a banking system in a team with a mentor. Developed a lot of landing pages.

React, Redux, WebSockets, Gulp, Node.js, Ruby.

Education



Frontend Pro Sep 2017 - Dec 20

Course certif



Frontend Bas Jul 2017 - Sep 201

Course certif



Computer Engineer
Aug 2017
Dnipro National University

Highlights

I'm familiar with fast prototyping and release MVP for early test ideas in the real world. It took me about 3 months to analyze requirements, set up development flow, and create the first social discovery MVP (with paying customers) version of the latest released project.

I've hacked a game dedicated to the contest at OdessaJS while sitting at the OdessaJS conference